http://www.bellevuemassageschool.com/privacy-policy

Mobile MenuAboutMission StatementInstructors and StaffCulture and FAQsNews and EventsContact UsAdmissionsProgramsMassageReflexologyEstheticsTransfer StudentBastyr IntensiveTuition and CostsRegistrationIntroductory ClassesContinuing EducationCE CalendarClassroom RentalStudent ClinicBook NowWhat to ExpectHealth Release FormsCancellation PolicyGraduate ServicesJob ListingsTranscript RequestSUBMITPrivacy PolicyBreadcrumbsHome Privacy Policy Washington Spa Academy LLC (aka Bellevue Massage School) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of the Washington Spa Academy LLC Website.Information CollectedIn order to access certain portions of the Website, users must register and provide certain voluntary information about themselves. The Website may collect and store information about its users: during user registration for such features of the Website and through the use of "session cookies". A session cookie is a non-persistent cookie that is deleted from the computer’s cache upon leaving a particular website.Use of InformationWashington Spa Academy LLC will not reveal to any third party a user’s personal information provided to us through the Website except in the following circumstances:We have your permission or consent to share the information;We need to share your information to provide the product or service you requested;We are responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.Using email addresses provided at registration or otherwise, Washington Spa Academy LLC may periodically send out email newsletters or other relevant information to our users about services and products offered by Washington Spa Academy LLC. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive email from Washington Spa Academy LLC by contacting us.Upon request, Washington Spa Academy LLC will remove user information from any lists or permit users to "opt-out" of any further email contact from Washington Spa Academy LLC.GeneralWashington Spa Academy LLC uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us by our users secure and to disclose such information only after obtaining permission from the user (except under the circumstances discussed above).If you choose to visit the Website, your visit and any dispute relating to privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Washington. Washington Spa Academy LLC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, the Website and the terms, conditions and notices under which the Website is offered. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these terms and conditions.From our AlumniThe best school I have ever been to, and locally owned. Awesome teachers and staff, our group had a lot of fun! They helped me find me a job immediately with an awesome spa, and have answered any questions I had post graduation. If you are looking for a new career as a massage therapist I highly recommend Bellevue Massage School.- Tyler, 2017 GraduateThe teachers at BMS are caring and knowledgeable, and the small class sizes mean a lot of 1-on-1 attention!- Jeff, 2017 GraduateMenuSUBMITHomeSitemap
